

Ivan Hale

Github github.com/ivanmhale
Design portfolio
ivanmhale.github.io/ivanmhale
Email ivanmhale@gmail.com

Summary

Software enthusiast, specializing in making web development. Passionate about making the web a better place for humans, as well as open-source technologies. Curious about machine learning, data science, and creating the next layer of abstraction with them.

Work Experience

Full Stack Engineer at Revature: 2019 - Present

- Front end/full stack engineering
- Microservice specialization
- Agile experienced
- Web design

Jr Software Developer at IC-CAP: 2018 - 2019

- Web design
- Front end development
- Database design

Freelance work: 2018 - 2019

- Web design and development
- Self-taught
- Worked directly with product owners

Education

Chattanooga State, General Engineering, graduated May 2017

Top Skills

Full Stack development Microservices database design Front-end engineering CI/CD laaS/Baas Web design agile + scrum REST/Graph API

Technical Experience

Node, React, Angular Express, Spring CSS3, Sass, Less TypeScript, ES6 REST, GraphQL JUnit, Jest, Mocha Hibernate, TypeORM SQL, MongoDB Eureka, Zuul, Hystrix Jenkins CI/CD Docker (beginner) AWS (beginner)

Professional References

- Christopher Klapp: R&D Engineer, Distant Shores Media, christopher@klapp.name
- John Madakacherry: Project Manager, 3rd Eye MobileVision, madakacherry@gmail.com
- Jay Chaudhary: Full Stack Engineer, Revature, jay.t.chaudhary@gmail.com
- Shahen Melkonian: Full Stack Engineer, Revature, shahen.r.melkonian@gmail.com